[Flying over to the ancient land of Egypt]
A mysterious country.
Wow, I'm really in Egypt.
The six of us look cool,
all dressed up and walking over.
[Six global idols]
It kinda feels like we're kings.
[But]
That’s where it ends.
[The two fates that lie before them]
[Prince]
[Either a dazzling prince]
I'm the prince! I'm the prince!
[Pauper]
I'm really a pauper now.
[Or a miserable pauper]
It's my first time eating
bread that doesn't taste like anything.
[A brutal fate of fighting]
Will you be a prince or a pauper?
[for status begins]
Oh, I'm a prince today too.
[Prince: 2, Pauper: 0 - DAWN]
Oh, I must be royalty.
I'm not like a criminal or anything.
[Prince: 1, Pauper: 1 - LEETEUK]
My name is Princess.
[Prince: 1, Pauper: 1 - SHINDONG]
I’m not happy.
Yesss!
I’m lying down for
the first time in 48 hours.
[Prince: 1, Pauper: 1 - JOHNNY]
Wow!
Wow, JOHNNY, today…!
Being a prince is really nice.
[Prince: 1, Pauper: 1 - YOHAN]
Oh, this is cheating!
Don’t go offbeat!
[And...]
Where do you keep going?
[The pauper expert...]
Where are you going?
[Prince: 0, Pauper: 2 - JISUNG]
I’m a pauper expert.
I'm a Paupert.
[Pauper life = zero stamina]
I have no energy.
Why am I so tired?
Ugh, whatever.
Let's just sleep.
[Scarier than poverty]
I'm desperate, struggling, and left with nothing, right?
[An impoverished heart]
I was getting so annoyed.
- I don't wanna see it anymore.
- Yeah, it's so annoying.
[I can’t live as a pauper anymore]
No matter what, I will become the prince.
[The stage for the 3rd status mission]
Wow! Wow!
[Luxor Temple]
Now it really feels like I'm in Egypt!
Wow, it’s really huge!
Wow, this is overwhelming,
like the vibe.
- Right?
- It's truly mystical.
I'm kinda getting chills.
Wow, this scale is massive.
Wow, we must be doing something here.
It's gonna be epic.
[Right in front of the temple]
This is a place known as the Avenue of Sphinxes.
[Unfolding on the Avenue of Sphinxes]
Starting right now in this place,
The Sphinx's Riddle!
We'll begin the mission.
[A mission with a total of 3 rounds]
The quiz is spread over 3 rounds.
[1R / Egypt] [2R] [3R]
Every round features a different category.
[Round 1 Rules]
Round 1 is…
The 15 Sphinxes lined up on the left
[1 2 3 4 5 ... 15]
have questions prepared.
[OB VS YB]
Team OB and Team YB will start
[The teams will start at opposite ends with the same questions]
at the opposite ends and tackle the same questions…
[They'll move towards the center after solving the questions]
The team that arrives first
[The team that answers the center question wins]
and solves the 8th riddle will win Round 1.
[If you don't know it, use your body!]
Get it together!
- Answer!
- Success!
[Experienced OB VS]
Wow!
- Answer!
[Hot-blooded YB]
Answer!
We got it right!
I'll definitely be a prince here.
Let's do it!
Let's become princes for real!
I really want to do it!
This is driving me crazy!
[The 3rd status mission with fate on the line!
It begins now!]
[CHAPTER.5
Tie up the camel and leave it to God]
[The Sphinx’s Riddle]
Once you've slept at the prince's accommodation…
[Ready for Round 1]
The treatment is totally different!
I feel like it'd be totally different.
[JOHNNY] After we wrap today,
let’s grab a beer and call it a night.
We have to, we have to.
I'm craving pasta…and pizza.
[The status mission begins on the path
where the sphinxes share the moonlight]
[Team OB / Team YB]
[They move to opposite ends of the row of sphinxes]
[OB / YB]
[Ready to roll]
[Sphinx’s Riddle, Round 1]
Alright, first question!
[Category: Egypt]
Give it to us!
Read it, read it, read it.
"Say the English spelling of Egypt."
The English spelling of Egypt.
[DAWN takes a shot]
E-G-Y-P-T.
Wrong!
??Why??
Egypt?
[The spelling for Egypt]
It’s E-G-Y-P-T, though?
[Brain freeze]
[Staff] Everyone,
you have to read the question carefully.
(Bringing their heads together)
The English spelling…
The English spelling of Egypt…
The English spelling?
The English spelling of Egypt...?
E...
[Fidgeting with the quiz paper]
[Backwards]
Oh, backwards.
- Ugh, this is annoying.
- Backwards, backwards, backwards!
[Just looking at the front of the quiz paper,
E-G-Y-P-T is correct]
[But when you open up the paper…?]
T-P...!
[Only LEETEUK
and SHINDONG have a chance]
Oh, what?
[Team YB also
gets the same question]
Spell Egypt in English.
- Backwards, backwards!
- Backwards?
[Team YB checks the
inside of the quiz paper right away]
It's asking for
the English spelling of Egypt backwards.
- Egypt… Do you know it?
- Oh!
T!
(EGYPT backwards…)
Egypt…P!
(This one's a job
for the Chicago hot guy)
Y!
G! E!
Correct!
[To the next Sphinx!]
Awesome!
Oh wow,
JOHNNY, you're crazy!
[2. Sphinx cam]
"The Egyptian flag has
an animal in the center."
- "What animal is it?"
- An eagle!
Correct.
[3. Sphinx cam]
[JISUNG gets it right in a flash]
Nice! Nice! Nice! Nice! Nice!
"You all visited
three pyramids on the first day."
"Who owns the biggest Pyramid?"
- Pharaoh.
- Sphinx.
[JISUNG takes a shot]
Ramses II!
[JOHNNY takes a shot]
King @#%$%?
[JOHNNY & JISUNG fail]
Wrong!
[YOHAN has the last chance]
I don't know it, I don't know it.
[Since they failed, 5 squats]
Get it…
[Creak, creak]
Get it…No, wait.
Get it together!
Get it together! Get it together!
[Sit down! Stand up! Down! Crazy!]
[The sunglasses jolt wildly
with the sudden vertical movement]
[They rush over to the next Sphinx]
But wait, is it Pharaoh?
Oh, it's Pharaoh!
"The Sphinx, the guardian spirit
that stands guard in front of the pyramid"
"has the body of a ____
and a head of a ____."
[What goes in the blanks?]
Answer!
[YOHAN takes a shot]
The body of a lion with a human head!
Correct!
[Young blood, Team YB charges ahead early]
Hurry up, you go first!
[Meanwhile]
You try first, LEETEUK!
[Team OB is still confused about the spelling]
Hold on, wait. Since it's Egypt…
- Success!
- Okay!
[Team OB finally heads
to the next Sphinx]
Here’s the next question.
[2. Sphinx cam]
"The Egyptian flag has
an animal in the center."
"What animal is it?"
An eagle!
- Correct!
- Okay, got it!
[3. Sphinx cam]
Okay, got it! Hey, we're good at this.
[Team OB also]
Yeah, well done!
[has studied quite a bit]
Okay, show us!
"You all visited"
"three pyramids on the first day."
"Who owns the biggest Pyramid…"
Answer!
[SHINDONG takes a shot]
Ramses!
Uh, isn’t it?
[DAWN takes a shot]
Khufu!
Correct!
- Okay, nice job!
- Wow, that’s awesome!
[Straight to the next Sphinx]
Hey, DAWN!
- DAWN, you’re a genius!
- Good job, good job, good job!
[4. Sphinx Cam]
Hey, when did you see all that?
[Falling for his smart younger brother]
Oh, it was King Khufu.
- King Khufu was the biggest…
- Oh, right!
"The Sphinx, the guardian spirit that stands guard
in front of the pyramid has the body of a ____…"
A lion's body with a human head!
Correct!
- Wow!
[Whoaaaaa! DAWN is an Egypt expert]
Hey, hey, hey, DAWN!
[5. Sphinx Cam]
Hey, hey, hey! You're amazing!
"To seduce Rome's Mark Antony,
Cleopatra drank"
"a special drink."
"What was the recipe?"
"Vinegar plus…"
What could it be?
Vinegar plus…
[Checking Team YB's location]
[Vinegar and what…?]
Vinegar plus…
What did they
drink a lot in Egypt?
What kind of drinks
do they have in Egypt?
(Team YB also has the same question)
"To seduce"
"Rome's Mark Antony,
Cleopatra drank"
- "a special drink."
- Oh, wait.
"What was the recipe?"
Vinegar and…?
[Since you’re curious,
here’s the answer]
[Answer: Pearls]
[A hint for the tough question]
Let’s hear the hint first.
- Do you want the hint?
- Yes.
[Hint]
It’s expensive.
Should we each take a guess?
Go ahead, go ahead.
[Both teams are stuck on question 5]
Vinegar and…
[Heavy metal]
Lead.
Wrong.
[JOHNNY’s turn]
Vinegar and grapes.
Wrong.
[YOHAN takes a shot]
Mullet roe.
[Final chance]
Wrong.
Get it together!
Get it together! Get it together!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- Apple, lemon!
- Let's just say anything!
- Hurry and say it, just hurry and say it!
- Oh, wait! Hey!
Hey, on the way here,
didn’t we say
there were lots of
tangerine shops around?
- Hurry and say it.
- Should we go with oranges?
- Did we say oranges?
- Just hurry and say something.
- Did we???
- We didn't, we didn't!
- Orange!
- Wrong!
[Their bodies move totally out of sync]
Start! 1!
- 2!
- We have to shout the chant!
[Unintentionally doing the wave]
Start! 1! 2!
- We have to shout the chant!
- Get it together!
Chant, start!
[Happily]
Get it together!
- Get it together!
- 2!
- 3!
- Get it together!
- 4!
- 5!
Hurry up!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Ancient Egyptians…Oh! “It’s said that
ancient Egyptians were serious about odor elimination.”
“What item did they invent first in the world?”
Perfume!
Wrong!
Soap?
[Answer: Toothpaste]
Say anything!
I don’t know!
[When your body’s good, your mind’s at ease]
Get it together! Get it together!
Get it together!
[Team YB arrives just before the final 8th question]
(The final Sphinx)
[Answer: Toothpaste]
“What item did they invent first in the world?”
Answer!
Perfume!
Wrong.
Diffuser.
Just say something quickly!
Soap!
Wrong!
Start!
Get it together! Get it together!
- Get it together!
- 3!
- Get it together!!
- 4!
Get it together!
He didn't do it!
Again!
- LEETEUK only did it 4 times.
- Come on, man!
Start!
[Feeling rushed while checking on the youngsters]
Get it together!
- That's good, that's good!
- Get it...
"The Pyramids, one of
the Seven Wonders of the World,"
"were built by manually moving
stones weighing 2.5 tons each"
"over the course of 20 years,"
"For the construction workers at the time…"
[What two things were given instead of money?]
Instead of money?
Oh! Beer!
Oh! Oh!
[Beer and bread]
Agh! Bread?
- Correct!
- Wow, seriously!
[Natural dopamine]
Wow, seriously!
[Team YB arrives at the 8th Sphinx first]
[Keeping tabs]
[Final question]
"Cleopatra VII was…"
[reportedly so intelligent that]
[she was able to speak 9 languages]
…so intelligent.
[Say "Thank you" in 9 languages]
"Thank you" in 9 languages. Okay!
(Chinese)
Xièxiè.
(Japanese)
Arigatou gozaimasu!
(English)
Thank you.
Gamsahapnida.
(Portuguese)
Obrigado.
[*One person has to say all 9 languages]
One person has to say them all! Again!
Okay, I'll do it.
(English)
Thank you.
(Chinese)
Xièxiè.
(Japanese)
Arigatō gozaimasu.
Korean, Korean, Korean!
(Korean)
Gamsahapnida.
Uh…
(Portuguese)
Obrigado.
(Indonesian)
Terima kasih.
Oh!
(Spanish)
Gracias!
Oh!
Uh…
Ugh, this is driving me crazy!
[Team OB is still on question 7]
Given instead of money?
I saw it over there earlier.
Rice…
And salt.
Clothes.
- Something to eat?
- Stone?
Is it stone?
Clothes, stone.
- Wrong!
- Let's start!
[Team OB doing the squats VS]
Get it together!
[Team YB answering the last question]
Get it together! Get it together!
(Spanish)
Oh, gracias!
[Just two more countries to go...!]
Oh!
Uh…
- Uh…
- Uh, this is driving me crazy!
[Please...]
This is driving me crazy!
Okay, we’ll count down now.
[As the silence stretches on...]
5, 4, 3…
- 2, 1.
- Please, please!
[They totally blank out on
saying "Thank you" in two more languages]
- Let's just…
- Hurry, just hurry!
[Especially loud]
Get it together!
- Get it together!
- Oh, this isn't it.
[Showing the most perfect and beautiful]
Give us the question! The question!
[squats]
Get it together!
[The last question doesn't have a squat pass]
You have to give us the question.
You have to get
the last question right.
[The two teams face off on the last question]
"Cleopatra VII was"
"reportedly so intelligent that
she was able to speak 9 languages."
[You can only win by getting the answer right!]
"Say 'Thank you' in 9 languages."
(Korean)
Gamsahapnida.
And…
(Japanese)
Arigatou gozaimasu!
And then…
(Spanish)
Gracias.
And…
(Italian)
Grazie mille.
(Emergency meeting)
That's Italian.
Next…Uh…
(Thai)
Khop khun khrap.
(Emergency meeting)
Next…uh…
(Chinese)
Xièxiè.
Next…
I already said that one.
(Arabic)
Shukran.
- Next…
- We said all 7 though?
- 7.
9...
How many was that?
- 5, 4…
- 2 more…Where are they?
- 3…
- No idea, no idea, no idea.
- 2, 1.
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Fail.
- Gracias!
[Failed due to time running out]
[Team YB's JISUNG goes for the second attempt]
Go for it!
Oh, you have to do one each?
(Portuguese)
Obrigado.
(Spanish)
Gracias.
(Korean)
Gamsahapnida.
(Chinese)
Xièxiè.
(Japanese)
Arigatou gozaimasu.
Terima kasih.
[Pop quiz]
What language is "Terima kasih"?
[Smart]
Indonesian.
(Thai)
Khop khun khrap.
(English)
Thank you.
- He stopped! We got it!
- 1!
[Just need to think of one more…!]
5, 4, 3…
[Ich liebe dich]
Ich liebe dich!
- Ich liebe dich!
- Whoa!
Huh???
- Rihidibidip.
- Rihidibidip?
!@#$%^%??
Wait, hold on.
[Dibidibidip??]
Hey, he doesn't know it! Hold on, hold on!
[Ich liebe dich]
That means "I love you."
["I love you" in German]
That's "I love you."
[Their victory
was right in front of them…]
We just need to say "Shukran."
No, that’s not it, no.
[Team OB SHINDONG's attempt]
Okay, SHINDONG, your turn.
(Korean)
Gamsahapnida.
(Japanese)
Arigatou gozaimasu.
(Chinese)
Xièxiè.
(Arabic)
Shukran.
(German)
Danke.
[18 years of tour experience...
He's unstoppable]
(Spanish)
Gracias.
(Thai)
Khop khun khrap.
(Indonesian)
Terima kasih.
(French)
Merci beaucoup.
- 9!
- We're done.
That’s it, we’re done.
Round 1
[Round 1: Egypt Quiz]
goes to Team OB!
[It's a party for Team OB!]
[While the vibe
fizzles out for Team YB…]
Wow…Like this?
Hahahahahaha!
[Don’t give up]
But it's only for Round 1.
[We still have two rounds]
Yeah, Round 1.
[left in the game!]
A total of 3 rounds, a total of 3 rounds.
[After winning the first round,]
But the questions weren’t what I was expecting.
[Team OB is super upbeat]
DAWN is really good at this.
[Can’t stop grinning]
DAWN got them all right! Wow!
He's the best!
Wow, DAWN is good!
[Feeling down, but now's not the time for that]
Oh, amazing!
- Wow!
- It's okay, it's okay. We can do it. We can do it!
For about 10 minutes…
For about 5 minutes, I couldn't believe it.
I couldn't remember the last one!
But the last one was "Shukran!"
I said "Shukran"
so many times that day.
I couldn’t remember "Shukran,"
and that was a real bummer.
We would've won
if I said "Shukran."
- I'm so bummed I couldn't say "Shukran."
- Oh, shukran.
Such a bummer.
Ugh, it's seriously
such a bummer!
Seriously such a bummer…
I even counted
all the statues in the temple.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You really…
- There were 17 inside.
[The madness born from deprivation]
Then 18, 19, 20, 21, 23, 24…
Ugh, I counted them all!
You re-re-re...!@#$?
You really want to be a prince.
I really want to be a prince!
This is driving me crazy!
I shouldn't linger in the past,
but I'm so bummed about this.
[Symptoms of Pauper JISUNG’s dark side]
Why didn’t I say "Shukran?"
[Talking way too much]
Shukran… Ugh…!
[JISUNG, we get you...]
[Disappointed + upset + down + gloomy]
Shukran, shukran.
[Empty + hollow + heartbroken]
Ugh, shukran.
[Thank you to fans worldwide]
We know how to say "Thank you" in many languages.
We know way more words
than we thought.
[1:0]
Team OB won Round 1.
- There's still Round 2!
- That's right.
The category for Round 2 is…
[Nervous]
[A battle of speed for this round?]
Oh, I'm expecting a battle of speed for this.
[Round 2 Category]
This mission is
related to K-Pop.
- Oh, okay!
- Oh, this is not good.
[Brightening up]
Oh, okay!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
[Sighs]
Oh, this is not good.
- I'm really not good at this.
- This generation…
I'm really bad at this.
- You're bad at it? It's okay.
- Oh, really? It's okay, it's okay.
- We’ve got an expert here.
- Yeah, we’re good, we’re good
At one point, when I was doing
music shows, radio, and variety shows
[The man who ruled them all]
about three time a week,
[Self-proclaimed K-Pop expert]
so I really knew a lot.
I knew a lot of songs.
I knew a lot about
the members of groups.
I think it'll give us
the upper hand.
Wow!
[Grinning]
[Another K-Pop expert appears]
I believed I knew a lot about K-Pop.
[YB has the upper hand over OB]
I thought I probably knew more
than the older members.
[Confident]
I thought I could totally do this well.
- Prepare well…
- Yes.
[Staff] and I'll see you
at the Sphinx on the other side.
- K-Pop?
- This is fun, this is fun!
[The Round 2 quiz will]
Do we have to head back that way then?
[take place at the Sphinx on the right side]
Yeah, we have to go that way.
Hey, you're so good at this.
[Both teams move
to the Sphinxes at the end]
JISUNG, do you know K-Pop well?
I do know it pretty well.
Then I think we can do it.
- Do you know it, JOHNNY?
- I really don't know.
Then JISUNG,
we're counting on you.
But I think Team OB
will do even better…
Oh, but that side…
Team OB even has
a hand on the old stuff too.
[If we don't know, let's just do squats]
If we don't know it, let's just squat right away.
Exactly, right away.
[Tension rises]
This is a speed game.
Now, there's definitely tension.
[No turning back now]
I didn’t feel like we were gonna lose.
[Who'll win Round 2?]
I wanna make the score 1:1.
[OB & YB]
Alright, let's begin.
[Ready to roll]
[Round 2: K-Pop Quiz, START!]
Please give us the questions.
"Calculate the number of members."
tripleS, CORTIS…
I don't know this for sure.
[tripleS x (CORTIS + ALLDAY PROJECT) =?]
[FYI: In South Korea, tripleS is]
[a girl group
with the most members ever]
- tripleS, CORTIS…
- 24 people.
Wait, 24 members?
Hold on,
CORTIS and ALLDAY PROJECT…
ALLDAY PROJECT has 4 members.
Both are… CORTIS…
- Aren't there 5 members?
- There are 5. There are 5 members.
5…There are 5?
CORTIS has 5 members.
ALLDAY PROJECT also has 5 members.
[Team OB has the same question]
"Calculate the number of members."
tripleS.
- tripleS.
- Times…
How many members
are in CORTIS?
- CORTIS has 5 members.
- So 5 members and…
- ALLDAY PROJECT has 4 members.
- 4 members.
- 9.
- tripleS…
- tripleS has 23 members.
- 9.
9 times 23.
- Aren't there 23 members?
- I think so, I think it's 23.
ALLDAY PROJECT has 4 members.
- There are 5 members!
- Oh, there are 5!
- There are 5 members.
- So, 10! It's 10.
[The answer to 23 X (5+5) is 230?]
Then, 230!
- There are 24 members?
- Yeah, 24 members.
[24X(5+5)]
[230 VS 240]
[Which one’s the right answer?]
[CORTIS]
[5 members]
[MARTIN, JAMES,
JUHOON, SEONGHYEON, KEONHO]
[ALLDAY PROJECT]
[5 members]
[BAILEY, TARZZAN,
YOUNGSEO, WOOCHAN, ANNIE]
[tripleS]
[Kaede, Lynn, SoHyun, Xinyu, Sullin]
[SeoYeon, JiYeon, Nien, Kotone, Mayu]
[SooMin, NaKyoung, HaYeon, JiWoo, SeoAh]
[DaHyun, YeonJi, JooBin, HyeRin, ChaeYeon]
[ChaeWon, ShiOn, YuBin, YooYeon]
[24 members]
[tripleS x (CORTIS + ALLDAY PROJECT)]
[24 members x (5 members + 5 members)]
[Answer: 240]
[SHINDONG's attempt]
230!
[Incorrect]
Wrong!
[JOHNNY's attempt]
240!
[Team YB]
Correct!!
It was multiplication?
- Oh, wow.
- It was multiplication?
It must be 24 members, so 240.
[DAWN's attempt]
240!
- Success!
- Okay!
[Team OB quickly heads to the 2nd Sphinx]
We got it, we got it!
[RIIZE - NMIXX + TWS - STAYC]
"Calculate the number of members."
RIIZE has 7 members.
- 6 members! 6!
- 6 members.
- NMIXX has 6 members.
Doesn't TWS have 5 members?
5 members.
RIIZE minus NMIXX, TWS, STAYC.
- RIIZE has 6 members.
- RIIZE…
- 6 members.
- 6 members minus…
- What about NMIXX?
- NMIXX has 9? 8??
It's not…
[6 members!]
Then, are there 6 members?
5 members.
I think STAYC has 6.
Then…
[6-6+5-6]
6 minus…
[YOHAN's attempt]
-1!
Wrong!
Just try 0.
[JISUNG's attempt]
0!
Correct!
[Guessed and got it right]
TWS, TWS…
Aren't you supposed to add first?
[???What are you saying???]
No, no, no, no, no.
No, this is zero.
TWS… TWS has 5 members.
TWS.
STAYC has 6…
[SHINDONG's attempt]
-1!
- Wrong!
- I guess it's not.
- Try 0. 0!
- 0!
- Correct!
- Okay!
[Golden Rule: Always guess 0 for short-answer questions]
0 was right!
[3. Sphinx cam]
"Name the youngest members of
the following idol groups in order."
"RIIZE, TEEN TOP, 2PM,
LE SSERAFIM, GIRL'S DAY, miss A."
[Thrown off by the increased difficulty]
miss A…Wait a sec.
[RIIZE]
ANTON.
[TEEN TOP's NIEL]
Wrong!
[We're in trouble…!]
Earlier…
[A tough question even for Team OB]
The youngest member.
- Wow, I have no idea.
- The youngest member is…
Alright, it's ANTON.
[TEEN TOP]
RICKY.
Wrong.
[Last attempt]
RIIZE, ANTON.
[TEEN TOP]
Thunder.
Wrong.
Get it together!
Get it together! Get it together!
Our strategy is
just to brute force it.
Let’s do squats fast
and get the next question quicker!
[Dashing to the next question]
"Name the leaders of
these idol groups in order."
[JOHNNY's attempt]
TXT's YEONJUN.
Wrong.
[Oh, right]
SOOBIN!
Oh, okay.
[TXT]
SOOBIN.
[MONSTA X]
MINHYUK.
Wrong.
Sigh... What was it?
[TXT]
SOOBIN.
[MONSTA X]
KIHYUN.
Wrong.
[It's okay,
everything's going according to plan]
Get it together! Get it together!
[Meanwhile,
one person misses the beat]
Get it together!
[Panting]
Get it together! Get it together!
Get it together!
My thighs feel like
they’re gonna explode!
[Complaining about the pain
after two sets of squats in a row]
This is a lyric interpretation question.
"In 2NE1’s 'I AM THE BEST',"
"what time is the speaker
scheduled to meet?"
8:30!
[The outcome of confidently blurting it out
right after reading the question]
[8:30]
Correct!
[KIM YOHAN nailed it]
[Proud]
One of my group members
really loves 2NE1.
He's always singing their songs.
[It's 8:00 right now, we're meeting at 8:30]
So as soon as I heard it, 8:30!
[Stuck in his brain]
I just said that.
[Thanks, buddy]
It's all thanks to that member.
[Team OB is still on question 3]
The youngest member…
Wow, I have no idea.
The youngest member is…
[RIIZE]
ANTON. It's ANTON.
[The youngest member of TEEN TOP is?]
I think it was CHANGJO…No, wait…
RICKY, RICKY, RICKY.
- ANTON, RICKY…
- 2PM's youngest…
Who was it in 2PM?
- CHANSUNG!
- Yeah, CHANSUNG!
[4th generation idol]
What about LE SSERAFIM?
In LE SSERAFIM…
- EUNCHAE!
And for GIRL'S DAY,
it was YURA.
For miss A…
Wasn't it…MIN?
No, MIN is the oldest.
- Oh really?
- SUZY!
[No idea]
Alright, let’s start from the top.
I'll do this one.
[RIIZE]
ANTON.
[TEEN TOP]
RICKY.
[2PM]
CHANSUNG.
[LE SSERAFIM]
EUNCHAE.
[GIRL'S DAY]
Wrong!
Oh, it's not YURA.
It's…It's…
[Dazed]
HYERI! HYERI!!
It's HYERI! HYERI!
Start!
[RIIZE]
ANTON.
[TEEN TOP]
RICKY.
[Again]
Wrong!
- Huh?
- Oh?
[Got TEEN TOP's youngest member wrong]
[RIIZE]
ANTON.
[TEEN TOP]
CHANGJO.
[2PM]
CHANSUNG.
[LE SSERAFIM]
EUNCHAE.
[GIRL'S DAY]
HYERI.
[miss A????]
Hold on.
[miss A]
SUZY.
[Will this be the right answer?]
Correct!
[Team OB did it]
Wow, it was CHANGJO! It was CHANGJO!
- I guess it was CHANGJO!
- I just blurted it out.
"Name the leaders of
these idol groups in order."
(Helpless)
TXT…This is…
Oh!
[TXT's leader is??]
Since it's TXT, it's him, him!
[Not YEONJUN!! But SOOBIN]
The soloist! YEONJUN! It's YEONJUN.
For MONSTA X, it's him.
- SHOWNU?
- SHOWNU, SHOWNU.
For SEVENTEEN, it's…
- SEVENTEEN is S.COUPS.
- SEUNGKWAN.
- S.COUPS! S.COUPS!
- Oh, S.COUPS!
For NMIXX, it’s…
- NMIXX?
- HAEWON, HAEWON, HAEWON!
[From the same 2nd generation]
What about Apink?
It's…It's…It's…!
- Bomi?
- It's not.
- Yoon Bomi.
- No, it's Chorong! Chorong!!
- Chorong!
- Chorong, Chorong, Chorong!
[Jewelry?]
Jewelry?
Park Jung-ah!
[Quickly passing through their idol peers]
Oh, okay, okay! Now go ahead!
[Glances]
You first, you first.
[Team YB is already closing in]
Get it together! Get it together!
[We must hurry…!]
You first, you first.
[TXT]
YEONJUN.
- Wrong!
- Oh, it's not?
[No clue right from the start]
It's not?
- YEONJUN.
- I have no idea.
Wow, that was tough.
In the end, we did squats.
[Like Team YB, when you don’t know,]
If you don't know it, you gotta do squats!
[make your body work for it]
Both teams were doing squats.
Someone do it.
[They’re almost here]
Anyone… I don't know
the names of anyone.
- Your friend's name, your friend's name.
- Uh…
CHUNGHA!
[Literally named anyone]
[Final chance]
Fail!
[Couldn't overcome TXT in the end]
Get it together!
- Get it together!
- 2!
- 3!
- Get it together!
- 4!
Get it together!
[As long as we moved on]
Oh, who was it?
[Meanwhile,
Team YB is zooming ahead]
This is a lyric
interpretation question.
"In CORTIS' 'FaSHioN',"
"where was the speaker
headed to go shopping?"
- What??
- We don't know.
- I really don't know.
- I have no idea.
Get it together!!
(Just dropped down)
(#2) (#3)
[Get it…!]
Get it together!
- Oof!
- Get it together!
[Get it together!!!]
Get it together!
- I really don't know this one at all.
- Oh, that hurts.
[The brain mission
turns into a physical challenge]
Oh, NMIXX is…It's…
[Team OB moves to the lyric interpretation spot]
This is a lyric interpretation question.
"In 2NE1’s 'I AM THE BEST',"
"what time is the speaker
scheduled to meet?"
Is there anything after that?
- The time scheduled to meet?
- "I AM THE BEST"…
"Right now,
we're meeting at 12:00."
Isn't it 12:00?
Or something like 12:59.
59 minutes?
Do they even specify the minutes??
[Must be a lunch schedule]
"I am the best, I am the best."
It's 5:30 right now.
- 5:30.
- Answer! Oh, I'll go first.
[This is the answer!!]
5:30!
Wrong!
[+1 hour]
6:30!
Wrong!
7:30.
[+2 hours]
7:30!
Wrong!
[Answer: 8:30]
Get it together!
[The appointment is quite late…]
Get it together! Get it together!
We're done, we're done.
[Just what time is it then…!!]
Hey, then what time is it?
[Q7. Guess the singer and song title]
This is guessing the song title.
Oh.
[Numbers]
Paper...?
Prayer!
[What song is this????]
Guess the singer and song title.
(Fidgeting)
What's the middle one? What is this?
It looks like paper.
[Random words]
SUPER JUNIOR!
Wrong!
Oh! Oh!
[JOHNNY’s attempt]
"ONE MORE TIME"?
Wrong.
(Quick energy boost)
Prayer…
[We'll just do squats]
I have no idea.
[DAY6]
Get it together!
["Time of Our Life" (To become one page)]
Get it together! Get it together!
[Save JISUNG…]
I’m dying.
(Can't squat)
[Team YB arrives at the last Sphinx first!!]
[Final question]
"Guess the song…" It's the same one.
"Name three in order."
- In order?
- Huh?
[Silence]
1 BANG...
2 BANG...
3 BANG...
BANG?
Is this a lightning symbol?
"BOOM"?
This is a bomb exploding, right?
[JISUNG’s attempt]
"BOOM".
[※ You have to name the singer and song title]
Please say the singer and song title in order.
[How are we supposed to know just by looking at this?]
The singer and song title?
Wow, I have no idea…
What could it be?
Oh, what is it? What is it??
[Q6 / Q7 / Q8]
[Team OB suddenly closes the gap]
This is a lyric interpretation question.
A lyric interpretation question.
"In CORTIS' 'FaSHioN',"
"where was the speaker
headed to go shopping?"
[SHINDONG’s attempt]
Dongmyo.
[Easily passed through]
SHINDONG, you're good at this, you're good!
[The gap narrows down to one question]
"Guess the singer and song title."
[Q7] [Q8]
Singer. Up.
- Once.
- In the sky.
[Will Team OB turn this around?]
No, it's once.
[Meanwhile, Team YB is still struggling]
What is it?
[Serious JISUNG]
Let’s really think this through once.
Let's keep thinking.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
I think there are 6 members.
7…members, no, there are 6.
A 6-member group?
(Looking away)
[Serious JISUNG mode ON]
6! 6!
Oh…!
[JOHNNY’s attempt]
JOHNNY!
BIGBANG's "BANG BANG BANG"
[Is this the right answer...?!]
Everyone, there are 3 songs.
Oh.
What??!?!
[Team OB is struggling next to them]
Just once…
Oh, say sorry, so just once…
- Oh.
- What?!
"BANG!"
After School’s "BANG!"
- Oh!
- IVE's "BANG BANG".
[Calm down]
One person can do it.
- Me?
- Oh, do it, do it.
After School's "BANG!"
IVE's "BANG BANG".
BIGBANG's "BANG BANG BANG".
[Wow, got a good feeling]
Correct!
- Wow!
- We won!
- Oh!
- It's over, it's over.
- Is it over????
- It's over?
- You won?
Wow!
- It's over?
- Yes.
Really?
Oh, really?
How are you
so good at this?
[YOHAN’s on fire]
Wow, After School's "BANG!" was insane.
- Wow, coming up with that was amazing.
- This answer was insane!
- What was the answer to this one?
- Hey, ask them!
[Shining at the crucial moment]
Answer! 8:30!
Correct!
[YOHAN leads his team to victory]
After School's "BANG!"
Correct!
We won!
The Sphinx’s Riddle.
Round 2: K-Pop Quiz
goes to Team YB.
You're good!
- Hey, well done!
- We're weak for things like this.
[Accepting defeat]
Oh, good job.
[We really did well]
We actually held our own this time.
JOHNNY's passion...
really moved me.
JISUNG said
he was moved by me.
[JOHNNY always led the way for JISUNG]
He felt how much I ran for him.
[Team YB did their best for each other]
That I ran faster than him.
Since I was a pauper in both
the first and second games,
the time has really come.
[Touched]
We seriously gave it our all.
But my thighs are
about to explode... Wow...
Oh…!
I can't do any more squats now.
No, JOHNNY!
You have to do it!
We have to get
the correct answers now.
[Changing the game plan]
[We have no choice but to get them correct now...]
We have to, we have to.
[Team YB rides high after winning Round 2]
Did you see our squat speed?
That was seriously next-level.
[Meanwhile...]
Compared to earlier,
- were we trying too hard to answer the questions…
- Right, right.
[No one knows?]
I seriously have no clue, no clue at all.
[Then do squats]
Get it together! Get it together!
I don't know!
[Team YB's strategy]
Get it together! Get it together!
[totally owned Team OB]
If you don't know,
just guess anything.
- Let's just get through it quickly.
- Let's power through with our bodies.
I suddenly started
feeling nervous.
These guys
[Team YB]
had the physique
and were pretty smart too,
so there was no way
for us to beat their speed.
They were definitely fast...
(Team YB kept running)
I was watching them coming,
and all of a sudden,
they were there in a flash!
"Wow, what are we
gonna do about this…?"
The current score is 1:1.
The final Round 3 will
be the most brutal
Avenue of Sphinxes.
Oh, what is it?
What is it?
[Why is that…?]
Each team
will start on the opposite ends
[The riddle questions have increased!]
and answer 15 questions.
- Wow.
[Sphinx’s Riddle]
[FINAL ROUND]
[8:8]
[15:15]
[Team OB]
[From opposite ends,]
[Team YB]
[each team must pass through 15 Sphinxes]
[and conquer the center]
[to claim the throne!]
The category for
the final Round 3 is…
[The last category
to decide this match is?]
[Membership]
It'll be questions about our members.
- Our members?
- Yes.
- Oh, it's about the team.
- Oh.
[Bad at everything except Egypt]
Oh… I'm bad at this.
Oh, no worries.
It's fine if you don't know.
I’m really bad at this.
I'm in trouble.
Wow…This is really bad…
I’m an INTP,
so I'm the type
that has no interest in other people.
That threw me off a bit...
Okay.
[LEETEUK and SHINDONG are just as worried]
But I think they know us better.
- I know, right?
- Right.
- About each other?
- Yes.
[On the other hand]
Okay!
[Confident JOHNNY]
All the questions
were taken
from the internet, YouTube, and Namuwiki…
- Oh, we can search?
- and written.
- No, they were written based on that.
- Oh, they were written.
Oh, this is gonna be really hard.
We're gonna have
to do a lot of squats.
[So, adding hints!]
Hints will be added starting Round 3.
- Oh, hints!
- Nice.
[Each person will take a shot, one by one]
when each member took a shot,
[Wrong!]
but the whole team failed,
you used to do squats, right?
[Retry + HINT]
That’s when the hints come in...
Oh, the hints are provided.
Pretty game-changing hints
will be given.
Oh!
If each person tries
and fails even with that,
[5 squats]
then we'll have you do squats.
- Oh.
- Let's get it together.
[More efficient to get the answers right!]
Let's try our best to get the answers right.
[The final showdown for each team!]
I'll see you in a bit for Round 3.
Let's go.
Let's go to the end.
[Which team will
take the throne tonight...?]
[This last category feels impossible]
Oh, a member quiz seems so hard.
- But seriously.
- It's tough.
[Thinking the questions will be super petty]
They’re probably insanely detailed.
It'll be really hard
if it actually comes out like this.
[They struggle to come up with possible questions]
The titles of songs NCT 127 promoted in 2023.
Yeah, we would not know that.
[Even that’s tough for Team OB]
I don’t even know my own stuff
I don’t know mine either.
Honestly, questions about me are the hardest.
[Turn]
But we are at
a bit of an advantage!
[Establishing dominance is a must]
Because we've actually
studied you guys a bit.
[Membership]
I was confident about this category!
We can totally win this!
[Team YB has followed]
Those guys have been around since our debut
[their seniors' journey in real-time]
and have seen us since they were kids.
[VS Team OB missed their junior's growth]
We didn’t get to see them in the middle in detail,
so I think
we'd know less about them?
(Simulation led by JOHNNY)
Namuwiki?
Let's find out the basics.
- Their ages.
- SUPER JUNIOR's debut.
LEETEUK was born in 1983.
That’s right!
SHINDONG was born in 1985, right?
DAWN was born in 1994.
Their debut year?
2005!
Their debut song?
[All coming out without hesitation]
"Twins (Knock Out)"!
If we just win this one…
JISUNG…If we just win this…
You can be a prince!
My thighs feel like they're about to explode,
but I really want this...
Ugh, I'm going crazy.
[A glimmer of hope makes
Pauper-Pauper JISUNG even more desperate...]
[Plod, plod]
Wow... God...
I’m not religious,
but I’m praying now...
(Nervous)
There…There aren't any bugs, right?
[Desperate,
but still scared of bugs...]
- Okay, we'll take our places.
- Yes.
[FINAL ROUND]
This is the final, everyone.
Oh, yes.
Let’s go!
Oh, 15 questions is brutal.
- My brain’s already starting to shut down.
- Yeah, exactly.
[Amidst a bit of tension]
[and serious determination in the air]
Even if we can’t walk tomorrow…!
Let's do it.
Let's become princes for real!
[Fueled by the leaders’ cheers]
We’ll go together,
and die together if we have to.
Running over there
is all the same.
- It's the same.
- Okay, okay. We just have to run fast.
- Go!
- Oh, okay!
[Team OB and Team YB are ready to go]
[3]
[2]
The first question…
[1]
Please!
[START]
"This is a membership quiz."
"Which body part is
JOHNNY the most confident about?"
His forearm.
Wrong.
Shoulder.
Answer!
Lats!
Wrong.
[Hint given after the first fail of Round 3]
Here's your hint.
[Hint]
JOHNNY is a sexy guy.
(Blink)
[Meanwhile, Sexy JOHNNY]
"It’s a membership quiz."
"Where is LEETEUK’s dimple located?"
Right cheek.
Wrong.
Left cheek.
Correct.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
(Answer confirmed)
[Team YB leads]
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
[Team OB is still on question 1]
JOHNNY is a sexy guy.
[Sexy guy]
Abs.
Wrong.
Body shape.
(Ready)
Sexy guy?
Butt.
Wrong.
[5 squats from the start]
Get it together! Get it together!
- Get it together!
- 3.
- 4.
Get it together!
The answer was lips.
Oh, lips! Oh!
[SEXY]
[Hurry to question 2!]
"This is a membership quiz."
"JOHNNY, who's American,
has the Korean name 'SUH YOUNGHO'."
"JOHNNY's full English name is…"
- JOHN.
(Say the full name)
It's not?
JOHN SUH.
- Fail
- Huh?
[Full name....??]
Full name?
[No clue]
JOHN SUH…
JOHNNY SUH.
Wrong!
Here's your hint.
[Similar to actress JUN JONG SEO's name]
It's very similar to actress JUN JONG SEO's name.
JUN JONG SUH.
JUN JONG SUH?
JOHN JO SUH.
- Wrong.
- It's not?
JOHN JONG SUH.
- Wrong.
- Oh, what?
- His last name is SUH.
- Yeah.
- Hurry, just say anything.
- His English name is…
JOHN…
JUNG! It's JUNG!
JUNG!
- SUH.
- Wrong.
- It's not?
[Real name: JOHN JUN SUH]
Get it together!
- What?
- Get it together!
- So frustrating!
- I'm tired right now.
- Get it together! Get it together!
[Today’s leg day]
I really don't know it. I really don't.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
[Meanwhile,
Team YB takes the lead]
"What job did LEETEUK
prepare for before his debut?"
[Caught off guard by the hard question]
Oh…
A carpenter.
Wrong.
[JISUNG's attempt]
A swimmer.
Wrong.
An architect.
Here's your hint.
It doesn't suit him.
This job doesn’t suit LEETEUK.
[Doesn't suit him]
An athlete.
Wrong.
[It really doesn't suit him]
A teacher.
Wrong!
[830,701 jobs that don't
suit him pass through their heads]
Uh…
[Really doesn't suit him]
A dentist.
Wrong!
["LEETEUK dreamed of becoming an announcer
as a student, but gave up due to low grades"]
[Answer: Announcer]
Get it together! Get it together!
Get it together!
- It doesn't suit him.
- It doesn't suit him?
[Heading to question 3 after some quick squats!]
I seriously don't know these.
Membership…Uh…
"LEETEUK has published
a book before."
"What’s the title of this book?"
(Published in 2020)
[Book written by LEETEUK]
[What’s the title of this book?]
[The title of the published book?]
"LEETEUK’s Special…"
"Hobby"!
Wrong!
"Habit"!
"LEETEUK's special posture".
Wrong!
I'll give you a hint.
The hint is "S, S"
- "LEETEUK's special…"
- "Meal".
"Meal".
- Correct!
- Oh, wow!
[Run / Run / Run]
[Q4. During SUPER JUNIOR's
"Bonamana" stage,]
[What’s the signature move
LEETEUK does often?]
A move he does often on stage.
[Showing off abs]
Revealing his abs!
Correct!
[Quickly nailed Q3,4]
We got it, we got it!
[Q1 / Q2 / Q3]
That's crazy, JOHNNY!
"This is a membership quiz."
[Q5]
[Team YB pulls ahead!]
[Team OB falls behind]
"This is a membership quiz."
"When JOHNNY eats mint,"
"he _____."
[What is _____?]
Vomit.
- Wrong.
- No.
Yawn!
Wrong.
When JOHNNY eats mint,
does he cough?
He sneezes…!
Saliva…
Oh, wait.
He sneezes.
- Correct!
- Oh, it's right!
[It's the most exciting
when you guess and get it right]
(Location check)
Alright, membership quiz!
"JOHNNY was born
in Chicago, Illinois, USA."
"Which of these brands
has never sold Chicago-style pizza?"
Do you know number 1?
UNO! I know this one.
- Yeah, just pick anything.
- UNO.
Wrong.
Oh, answer!
Papa John's.
- Correct!
- Okay!
Huh?
[Q1 / Q2 / Q3 / Q4 / Q5]
[Thanks to the foodie's stellar moves,]
[they're back to square one!]
That's right! This is how it should go.
"This is a membership quiz."
"What was LEETEUK’s drama debut?"
- School... It's something to do with school!
- School?
Isn’t it something
that happens at a school?
School?
I have no idea.
[When you scroll down
on Namuwiki,]
[LEETEUK’s drama filmography comes out]
[From the list,
his debut project was "All About Eve"]
[A blockbuster drama
with a peak rating of 48.3%]
[Legendary actor LEETEUK’s debut]
Hurry up, hurry up!
(2000)
[JISUNG / Born in 2002]
If there’s a question about the past or something,
[Born after LEETEUK’s drama debut]
I thought I'd be in trouble.
The SUPER JUNIOR members…
Back in the day!
[Team YB gets stuck on questions about the past]
Those questions were seriously tough.
"JOHNNY is famously known
as a webnovel fanatic."
"What is JOHNNY's favorite webnovel
that was even made into a drama?"
Wait, this is…
A webnovel...?
We didn’t even
have webnovels back then!
Oh, we did, we did!
[Old-timers]
Back in our day, we used to read on sites like Nownuri and Cheollian.
[Team OB gets tripped up by modern questions]
We had novels by Guiyeoni and stuff.
Like, "Romance Of Their Own"
was all the rage then.
(Another old-timer here)
That, that, that…!
There’s that famous webnovel author.
- Huh?
- It even became a drama.
(Probably Guiyeoni)
Was it Seoyeoni?
"Yumi’s Cells".
Wrong.
Ugh…
Oh, it’s a webnovel, right?
A webnovel?
"Moving".
Wrong.
Ugh, what was that again?
[Hurry and say it]
Just say anything! Anything!
No, that…what was it?
- Just spit it out!
- I don't know.
Oh!
[Let's just get the hint]
"I'm Sorry, I Love You"
Wrong.
[Meanwhile, Team YB]
So, a stage with all the SUPER JUNIOR members.
Uh…Oh…That…Uh…That…
- I don't know. I don't know at all.
- I think I've heard of it though…
The flying…
It's not "The Flying Superboard".
[Maybe]
It’s not "Flying SUPER JUNIOR", right?
Wrong!
I think we need the hint.
Let's get it then.
Let's just get it.
"SUPER JUNIOR School".
Wrong.
The hint is…
"All About ____"!
Oh! JOHNNY!
"All About SUPER JUNIOR".
Wrong.
Wow.
"All About Handsome Guys".
Wrong!
"All About…" "All About…"
"All About School".
- Wrong.
- Ugh!
[The answer is "All About Eve"]
Get it together! Get it together!
Get it together!
[Team YB clears Q5 first]
What was it then?
[Q1 / Q2 / Q3 / Q4 / Q5]
"Eve"? "Eve"?
"What’s SHINDONG’s IQ?"
- Uh…
- Oh!
- 100, 100!
- I don’t think we can solve this one.
Wrong!
(Still stuck on the webnovel one)
The hint is…
The lead actor is SONG JOONG KI.
SONG JOONG KI.
- "Descendants of the Sun".
- Oh!
- No! It's that!
- Wrong.
"Reborn Rich".
- Correct!
- That's right!
Alright.
"Where’s the mole
on KIM YOHAN’s face located?"
Above the left eyebrow.
- Correct!
- Yeah, that's right.
- Okay, correct!
[Q6, right on the first try!]
(Answer confirmation)
"KIM YOHAN has a unique
personal talent for playing an instrument."
[What is this?]
Oh! Answer!
Playing the recorder with his nose.
- Correct!
- Okay.
[Q7 / Q8]
Wow, how did you know that?
I think I saw it on a show.
"KIM YOHAN recently ordered
jajangmyeon, but had a delivery mishap."
"What was missing?"
The noodles.
Correct!
[A weird hunch]
[Speeding through Q6, 7, 8]
[Team OB Comeback]
- Just do it now.
- 140!
(Can go UP / DOWN)
UP!
(That high??)
- Correct!
- Wow! Let's go!
[Moving quickly to the next question]
[So desperate]
Whoa, careful, careful!
JISUNG, be careful!
[Sacrificing one knee is nothing
to become a prince]
Wow, there’s no way I know this...
"SHINDONG once appeared in
a movie called 'Attack on the Pin-Up Boys'."
"At the time, SHINDONG played
a member of the dance team."
[What’s the name of this dance crew?]
Dance SHINDONG!
Wrong!
This…
I don't think this will be right.
What? What?
Dandong.
Wrong.
[A tough question without a hint]
Taking a hint isn’t a bad idea either.
Dance club.
Wrong.
The hint is,
it's stronger than SUPER JUNIOR.
[SUPER JUNIOR < ULTRA JUNIOR]
[Answer: ULTRA JUNIOR]
Superman.
Wrong.
[Variety score: 100 points]
Super Senior!
Wrong
[Clueless]
Su…Ugh…
Supermarket.
Wrong.
ULTRA JUNIOR.
[What even is ULTRA JUNIOR?]
Get it together! Get it together!
Get it together!
[Misheard it in the middle of it all]
Infra Junior is a bit too much.
[Q8]
[Meanwhile,
ULTRA JUNIOR is in the lead]
[Q9]
"Whenever he feels awkward,
a certain part of KIM YOHAN's body twitches."
[What is this?]
Philtrum.
Wrong.
Cheekbone.
Eyebrow.
Wrong.
Hint.
[Hint]
It’s on your face.
It’s on the face.
Between the eyebrows.
Wrong.
Eyelids.
Forehead.
- Wrong.
- Ugh.
Okay, start!
[Answer: The corners of his mouth]
Get it together! Get it together!
Get it together!
Okay! We're fast right now.
We can take it slow.
"Former Taekwondo athlete KIM YOHAN
had a jinx where he had to wear"
"a specific pair of
underwear for every match."
"What animal is printed
on this pair of underwear?"
A lion.
A tiger.
[This one doesn’t look easy...]
Answer! Cat!
[And Team YB is…]
[Q8. What product
did SHINDONG sell out]
[during a home shopping broadcast to generate 2.1 billion won in sales?]
SHINDONG…home shopping…
A puffer jacket!
A long puffer jacket!
Correct!
[Team YB and Team OB
are just one question apart]
- Hey, come here, come here.
- Be careful.
"What’s the name of
the internet cafe SHINDONG ran?"
Oh, this…
- Dracula PC Castle.
- Oh, yeah, that's right!
(Confident)
Dracula PC Castle.
Correct.
[They nailed Q9 and Q10
on the first try and tied the game!]
[A. Bear]
Get it together!
[Doing squats after failing]
Get it together! Get it together!
My knees are gonna hurt later.
[Q8 / Q9]
[Q10]
[If one tries to catch up,]
[Q11]
[the other runs away again!]
[A fierce race where victory is close, but so far]
My knees are gonna hurt later. My legs are gonna hurt.
Hey, hey, hey! Hang in there!
We're almost there! We're almost there!
[Q10. SHINDONG apparently threw something
to the fans that he wasn't supposed to during a concert]
[What is this item?]
A cell phone.
- Wrong.
- No, it's not that.
[Keeping tabs]
That’s right.
"What is the item that
JISUNG often throws while dancing?"
A heart.
- Wrong.
- Uh, oh.
A wink!
Wrong.
He throws it.
Oh, ugh…
- Something he throws…?
- Yeah. Something he throws.
While dancing.
A kiss?
His eyebrows?
Wrong!
- Hint, hint, hint!
- What is it? What does he throw?
[Hint]
To bring the dance to life!
- Oh.
- To bring the dance to life?
Hair!
Hair strands!
Correct!
- That's right. I do that a lot.
- Oh, right.
[Quickly passing through without squats]
Because my dancing doesn't hit right.
A towel.
Wrong.
Here's a hint for you.
[Check]
It’s something on the body.
[Hint: Something on the body]
Underwear.
Wrong.
[Answer: Teeth]
- Oh.
- Body hair.
[Thumbs up]
Oh, a thumb! A thumb!
Wrong!
[Oh, now…]
Geez.
[So tiring…]
Get it together! Get it together!
Get it together!
We gotta go quickly!
We gotta go!
"What score did JISUNG get
on his 7th-grade math test?"
2 points.
Wrong.
0 points.
38 points.
- I'll tell you up or down.
- Okay.
3 points.
Up.
- No, somewhere in the middle.
- 30 points.
Down.
Oh, wait.
[3 < ? < 30]
Should we say 15? Or 20?
- Just pick anything.
- 20 points.
[When he was 14 and in 7th grade,]
Get it together, get it together
[he scored 16 points on a math test.]
Oh, I'm in so much pain. Hold on.
[Answer: 16 points]
Get it together! Get it together!
(We're going first)
I can't do it. I'm in so much pain.
"What is JISUNG's English name?"
JISUNG PARK!
Wrong.
JISUNG?
David Park.
Wrong.
- JISUNG?
- Yeah.
(Team contribution: zero)
[Team YB is busy, trying to catch up]
We gotta go quickly! We gotta go fast!
Stop!
He threw his water away.
[Q11. DAWN’s real name
is Kim Hyojong]
[Then, what number king
of the Joseon Dynasty was King Hyojong?]
- Tae-Jeong-Tae-Se-Mun-Dan-Se…
- What number king was Hyojong in the Joseon Dynasty?
(Don't know the kings after this)
I really wouldn't know this.
The 23rd king?
Wrong.
The 5th king.
[Putting his fingers down
for no reason]
[Current status]
[Q11 / Q13]
[Team OB is in the lead]
[Team YB will be in trouble
if they fall behind any further]
[Thinking hard]
The 17th king!
- Correct!
- Okay!
[JISUNG, nice!]
Oh! He was the 17th king!
[There will be
no more Pauper JISUNG]
[Q12. What dance style
does DAWN like?]
Poppin’!
Correct!
(Pure joy)
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[Q13. What's the maximum
number of burgers DAWN can eat?]
Two!
Correct!
[Thanks to JISUNG’s legendary move]
He knows the most about DAWN!
[Team YB flips the script]
[Q14. Which of these
is not true about DAWN?]
[1. Holds a Level 1
Word Processor Certificate]
[2. Holds a Level 2
Computer Skills Certificate]
[3. Holds a Western Cuisine
Cooking Certificate]
[4. Can do 45 push-ups
in 30 seconds]
- JISUNG?
- Oh! Hurry and say it! I think I know it!
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, hurry, hurry! Hurry and say it!
Chris.
Wrong.
I'll give you a hint.
There's a 1st-generation SM artist
with the same name.
1st generation?
[Hint: A 1st-generation SM artist has the same name]
TONY.
Wrong.
1st generation?
ANDY…AN…Oh!
ANDY!
Correct!
[Team OB is starting to panic]
Number 1!
Wrong.
Number 2!
Number 3!
Correct!
[Meanwhile, Team YB lucks out
with a multiple choice question]
[Q15]
[FINAL]
[Q14]
"JISUNG wants his last meal to be
______ and seasoned bean paste."
[What is ______?]
Pig's trotters!
Pork belly!
Boiled pork wraps?
[Hint]
It’s a vegetable.
- A vegetable.
- A vegetable?
Lettuce.
Perilla leaves.
- What is it?
- Cilantro?
Cilantro.
[Answer: baby napa cabbage]
Get it together! Get it together!
[Feeling rushed, but squatting again...]
[FINAL]
[Last question]
[Q15. DAWN’s conception dream was about]
[a young Buddhist monk
bringing _____ to his mother]
[What is _______?]
A car.
[A young Buddhist monk
brought a car…??]
Wrong.
The young monk…to his mother…
[Team OB is about to reach the final question too]
Get it together! Get it together!
Hang in there!
Just a little more, hang in there!
[FINAL]
Hang in there, just a little more!
[Both teams have
only one question left!]
[ROUND 1: Egypt Quiz]
Merci beaucoup.
[Team OB won first]
Round 1 goes to Team OB!
[OB / YB]
[1:0]
[ROUND 2: K-Pop Quiz]
After School's "BANG!"
IVE's "BANG BANG".
BIGBANG's "BANG BANG BANG".
- Correct!
- Wow!
[Team YB stays alive with a dramatic equalizer]
We won!
It’s over, it’s over!
- Oh, really?
- How are you so good at this?
Wow, After School's "BANG!" was insane.
[1:0]
This answer was insane!
[1:1]
But wow, that was seriously amazing.
[Everything comes down
to this last question]
"JISUNG has a life-defining, tear-jerker of a book
that he always packs when he travels."
[What is the title of this book that's been made]
It's been made into an anime and a movie…
[into an anime and a movie?]
"Harry Potter".
- Wrong.
- Ugh!
"Late Blossom".
- Wrong.
- Oh, come on!
"Dragon Ball".
Wrong!
A peach?
Wrong.
It's 3 syllables.
Anything!
A cat!
Wrong.
The hint is that
it's a very precious treasure.
- Treasure?
Treasure?
- Treasure
- Treasure?
A diamond.
[If diamond is correct,]
[becoming a prince
will be right before their eyes]
I'll give you a hint.
It includes a body part.
[A body part...?]
"I Want to Eat Your Pancreas".
Correct!
[Team OB clears the last question]
Great job!
- Where is it? Where is it?
- Why aren't you giving it to us?
Where is it?
Oh, here! Here it is!
[First to reach
the center statue wins]
When we did the math,
the other team…
Team YB was about
one question ahead of us.
I looked back
and thought,
"I need to sprint as fast as I can."
I looked out of
the corner of my eye as I ran.
"Oh! We won!
I'm finally becoming a prince…!"
[Which team will actually
claim the title of prince...?]
Hey, go, let’s go, let’s go!
[Team OB pulls off a last-minute comeback!]
Hey, we got it, we got it!
- Whoa
- Hey, we got it, we got it
Wait, wait, wait!
- 1, 2, 3!
- I'm the prince!
I'm the prince!
(Going off-frame in shock)
What's happening?
[The dream of a prince slips away before their eyes…]
Agh…
- We got it.
- We won!
- Wow!
[Team OB LEETEUK, SHINDONG, DAWN,
confirmed as the 3rd line of princes]
- Wow!
Oh!
[And…Team YB becomes paupers]
Oh, my legs gave out.
- My legs gave out.
- Oh, I'm so tired, so tired.
...I honestly
don’t remember anything.
People say that when the shock is
too big, you don't remember anything.
I don't remember a thing…
Because, if you just
did your best and lost,
it's like,
"Aw, what a bummer."
But I was like,
"I must win no matter what," and lost…
[Dizzy]
Wow…It was such a shock.
[Our JISUNG...]
[The 1st status mission: The Pharaoh’s Table]
Wow!
I’m the pauper...
Don’t lose our pace now.
[Became the first pauper from Day 1]
Oh, wow.
[The 2nd Status mission: The Solar Barque]
Wow!
I really don’t want
to be a pauper today!
Ack! Whoa! Hold on!
[Double pauper achieved]
Today is romantic, for sure.
Wow, I'm a double pauper…
A pauper-pauper.
No matter
[Today]
what happens tomorrow,
[Determined to become a prince no matter what...]
I’m gonna be a prince.
[Back to reality…]
I was stunned, like, "Oh, we lost."
[Triple pauper achieved…]
I'm a pauper…again.
Agh…
Honestly, at that moment...
I felt bad for JISUNG.
JISUNG has never
been a prince, not even once.
[The chance was right within reach...]
The opportunity was right there.
And that…
If only we had
done a little better...
I had that kind of regret.
Maybe LEETEUK, SHINDONG,
and DAWN were too slick…
They must've been too good.
I don't know
what was happening with the other team,
[Team YB swallows their disappointment]
but we really gave it our all.
Wow…
After getting the last question right…
Considering we're still older than them…
Did we run too excitedly?
I didn't even think about that.
(A bit embarrassed thinking back)
The way we ran to beat our little brothers…
[And our eldest brother...]
And they were like, "Isn't this too much, LEETEUK?"
[What can you do?]
It can't be helped.
I seriously
went all out like crazy.
[The verdict]
So yeah, it couldn't be helped.
[The Sphinx’s Riddle]
I was so surprised
[Game over]
by all the questions about JOHNNY today.
JISUNG, we really gave it our all.
[Staff] Did today help you guys get
to know each other better and grow closer?
- Yeah.
- It was so much fun.
It was fun.
So, today,
[Today’s princes]
Team OB is the prince!
Oh, he's like a king all the way.
[And standing out the most among them]
Wow, a king all the way.
The king of kings.
[Triple prince, DAWN]
It's seriously kind of weird!
[There's even a triple pauper too…]
I'm thinking about just moving here.
Oh, wait…
But what do we do?
- JISUNG...
- Sorry, JISUNG.
- JISUNG, sorry!
But seriously…
(Hurt Pauper JISUNG)
Guys, I saw you running here.
[The sprint of the apologetic brothers]
You weren't sorry at all.
Sorry. I just wanted
to sleep comfortably today.
Although it was
a short time today,
[Anyway, that’s it for today’s mission]
please enjoy the prince life and the pauper night.
We'll continue the trip tomorrow.
Thank you!
- Let's head out!
- Let's go!
Agh!
- LEETEUK is a prince twice in a row too!
- Seriously.
[Off to their accommodations to prepare for tomorrow!]
Oh, twice in a row.
- That was good.
- Oh, but my legs hurt.
My butt hurts.
[They return to the cruise
after a fierce mission]
[Something surprises WANGGEOZ?]
Oh my…! Hey, wait.
We're here!
- Their house is here. It's nice that it's close!
- Oh?
[Right in front
of the princes' cruise]
[The pauper's tent appears]
Oh, it's right here?
It's close!
[The announcement made just a moment ago]
Let me give you one last announcement.
The princes
can use the same
accommodation as yesterday.
[The same cruise accommodation from yesterday]
Oh!
[The paupers' accommodation is…]
And for the paupers,
due to an itinerary issue tomorrow,
[A new place?]
the accommodation changed a bit.
- Oh? Is it better?
- Yes.
[For the first time in 3 days of the trip!]
For the first time!
- Oh?
- No way…!
[A spot to watch the princes!]
You'll sleep while looking into the princes' lives…!
No way…Is it the sunbed?
No, the trees right in front…
[Or maybe the banana grove...?]
Oh, the banana grove?
[Next to the banana grove]
We’ll set up tents at the dock.
[Oh, come on!]
[While the paupers grumble loudly]
Ugh, seriously!
I ate bread there earlier!
[The princes are busy teasing them]
Hey, you're just going back home.
At least it's close.
What do you mean
just going back home?
(Can't hear anything from the shock)
You're just going back home.
- What do you mean "just going back home"?
- You said you ate there.
You're just going home.
- Isn't this a bit cruel? You can see everything!
- I knew this would happen.
[More shocking to see it in person]
Seriously…ugh…
Oh no!
[The princes only see the perks]
The view is amazing here.
Wow, this is so romantic.
[While the paupers only see the downsides]
But, seriously, do you know what the biggest problem is?
What is it?
It's so noisy over there.
[The biggest downside]
[The fancy banquet hall right next door]
[Let's enjoy the lively night in Egypt together]
Hey, but the music is loud and nice!
- The people there scream so much.
- Oh, but…
Was it set up like this
yesterday too?
[At least the staff pitched the tents for them today]
No, we set them up.
We set them up yesterday.
[And the one person who's seeing
the paupers' accommodation for the very first time]
[DAWN] How are 3 people
supposed to sleep in here?
[The blue-blooded prince
who's only slept on comfy beds]
[The pauper tent
feels so unfamiliar]
Alright, head inside!
- Goodnight!
- Okay, Pauper #1.
[The experienced paupers naturally walk in]
I was Prince #2 yesterday, though.
It's nice that
our accommodations are close by!
Is... is that so...?
Is that so?
I guess, yeah.
[The Paupert naturally heads into the tent too]
Oh, my legs hurt. Oh, my legs.
After being the pauper a few times,
[Now it feels like home]
It felt very familiar, stepping into the tent.
Hey, but it must be
nice and cool here.
[With mocking words of comfort]
Yeah, it's nice and windy today.
[and worry]
Hey, be careful! Don't get pushed toward the back.
Hey, but shall we finish up
[They leave their little pauper brothers]
our conversation from earlier here?
- LEETEUK, let's go.
- Let's go.
[The princes head to the cruise]
Good night!
- Bye!
- Sleep well!
Good night.
[Though the princes have left...]
What’s with the music!
- It's really loud! How are we supposed to sleep?
- They're just pumping up the music!
[No such thing as a dull moment in the pauper's tent]
A woodpecker on the left, and a club on the right.
I'm gonna go crazy.
We just went
straight into the tent.
But... the music
was just way too loud.
[The music and the lights were absolutely unbearable]
It was like a full-on festival.
The lights were super flashy.
[Couldn't resist and attended the party]
We got curious, so we went to check it out.
It felt kind of like a banquet.
The locals suddenly
appeared and started dancing.
[YOHAN feels out of his element here]
I can't do this!
[Standing still when everyone's dancing?]
It's awkward to stand around while everyone's dancing.
[I’m the main dancer of NCT DREAM, you know?]
So, I just threw in some waves,
and did stuff like this.
I did some finger-tutting.
I did stuff like that.
[A pro dancer steps up
at the Egyptian neighborhood dance party]
[And the one stealing
the spotlight behind him]
[Lost in the moment]
I did slightly bust a move or two.
[Born to be an idol]
I realized I'm quite the attention-seeker too.
[This kind of moment is the fun of traveling]
In the middle of all that, I'm sleepy.
- I'm really sleepy.
- Right, I'm a bit sleepy.
I just wanna sleep.
I just wanna sleep
even without a sleeping bag.
[Using a sleeping bag as a pillow tonight]
Should we go for that vibe today?
I think you're right.
It'll be comfier to use as a pillow.
But from what I can see,
- we'll use the sleeping bag when it gets cold at dawn.
- Oh, really?
[Still, let's just lie down for now]
But for now, let's just do it like this.
- Oh, like that.
- Okay, okay.
[The experienced paupers
lock up for the night]
Wow.
[No, but…]
This is actually comfy.
We're gonna sleep
with this music blasting?!
Like, isn't it too noisy?
I think I can sleep.
No, but this is so loud…
Honestly, this isn't so bad,
because on the first day…
[These two who were paupers on Day 1…]
Oh, wait…
This is legit pauper status.
[experienced the desert tent]
Are we seriously stranded here?
That was legendary.
[Just counting their blessings today]
This isn't bad at all.
- That’s why I’m feeling good right now
- Oh, really?
[The Day 2 pauper doesn't get it]
Oh, today… Well, yesterday was pretty okay.
- Day 2 paupers were just kings.
- If you were there yesterday,
- you would've loved it.
- Yesterday, it was king status.
No.
You’ve never been a prince before.
(Paupert)
Maybe that’s why…
I can see them back there!
I can see them totally loving it.
[Watching the princes across the river]
The first day was seriously legendary.
Oh, they're picking rooms!
[The princes inside the cruise]
Oh man.
- It just feels like my house now.
- Oh!
[So moved by the soft couch]
OH! Why is this sofa so comfy?
Wow, this is amazing.
- Let's pick our rooms.
- How did you pick yesterday?
[The princes will pick rooms again today]
We just put the keys here
- and played Rock-Paper-Scissors to decide.
- Oh, okay.
[Only SHINDONG switched in]
Oh, I'm the only new guest here.
[Feeling at home now]
If you want something to drink,
you can have a drink at night.
Excuse me!
[Naturally ordering a refreshing cola]
One Coke, please.
Two Cokes, please.
SHINDONG, are you good?
[Quickly adjusted]
One Coke Zero.
Okay, LEETEUK, you pick first.
[It's really time to pick rooms now]
I really want to sleep in the suite once.
- Oh!
- Oh, please!
[Goal: The one and only suite]
[Relaxed DAWN]
Oh, I have no attachment to it, LEETEUK.
[and Desperate LEETEUK]
The middle one!
- Okay.
- Alright.
[And the former pauper, who's happy with anything but the tent]
Since I'm right-handed, the right one.
We'll open them
at the count of three.
[Which prince will get the suite today?]
1, 2, 3!
Huh?
[The most earnest]
The suite!
[LEETEUK gets it!]
Yeah!!
[Before going to bed]
Okay, let's go.
- The colas are here. They're here.
- Oh, the cola.
[Refreshing cola time]
Wow!
We have to raise a toast.
[Cheers to the Day 3 princes!]
Congratulations, princes!
The prince life is so good.
[After chugging down
a refreshing glass of cola,]
So refreshing!
[the princes head off to rest]
Now, rest up!
Rest well, guys.
Alright, let's go.
[And out in front…]
This is so nice.
[The princes are drinking cola…]
I wanna drink some cola.
Drinks…
[Let’s just sleep!]
Oh, never mind. Ugh!
[Sleeping, even with a mouth as dry as a desert]
My mouth has no saliva left, but I'm just gonna sleep.
Me too.
It's kind of dry right now.
Should we turn this off?
[Lights out before bed]
Oh, yes.
If you click the switch…
- I know about it too.
- Nice, nice.
[Gotta get that club lighting at least once]
But doesn't this fit here?
Ha…
- I’m like…
- Oh, but like…
[Their eyes are closing even with the loud music]
But that's starting to sound like a lullaby now.
I know, right?
It feels like it's telling us to sleep now.
It was seriously so noisy,
but I was so tired
that even the noise
sounded like a lullaby.
[A pauper's night, as explained by the Paupert]
Even as paupers,
there's no time
to just sit around and complain.
[Just lie down and sleep]
Let's deal with it tomorrow, and right away…Yeah.
I passed out
the moment I lay down, so...
[A tough night for the paupers]
When you have a tough day,
[always means a deep sleep]
no matter the bed, the sleep is golden.
We’ve all done this
at least once now.
[The night falls on
the seasoned paupers...]
[The princes
head off to bed as well]
[LEETEUK] I'm using this room?
[Entering the suite with awe]
Wow!
Whoa, what is this! Whoa!
Wow, this is so nice.
[The best room during the 3 days in Egypt]
What do I do?
I can't believe I'm in a suite!
Oh, thank you.
[Nothing to do but be grateful]
Thank you.
Having peace of mind
is really important in life.
[Back during his pauper days,]
When I was a pauper on Day 1,
[he was a hothead]
I kept asking why it had to be like this.
[His interview on being a pauper on Day 1]
I honestly thought it was too much.
Like, this seriously isn't right.
It's just not right.
[But after becoming a prince]
But the moment I became a prince…!
[Empathy levels drastically rise]
"Oh, I get it now."
[Lesson learned from experiencing life as both prince and pauper]
Everything flipped 180 degrees.
People can be so cunning.
[SHINDONG returns as a prince after one day]
Oh, this is nice.
As someone who slept
in a tent the night before…
a bed and blankets,
[Even appreciating the ceiling and walls]
and the fact that everything's closed off around me is so great.
[Totally satisfied]
I slept so well.
[Even blue-blooded prince DAWN who's so used to it]
Oh, I'm a prince. I'm a prince again.
[The night passes
at the prince's accommodation]
[ALL or NOTHING]
[Day 3 status resets!]
[Heading to
WANGGEOZ’s final destination]
[Loved by the Pharaoh]
[The Gardens of the gods]
[Beneath the piercingly
blue water's surface,]
[the Red Sea,
home to countless marine creatures]
[And the unexpected scenery
beyond the shoreline]
[Home of the Bedouin tribe,
the masters of the desert]
[When the sky burns
with a fiery red sunset,]
[the desert transforms
constellations into a compass]
[Where the red desert
meets the blue Red Sea]
[A city full of
hot and cool surprises]
[HURGHADA]
I've never really looked at
vacation spots in Egypt
and really didn't know about it,
so I got curious
and looked up the area
we're heading to.
[Chill resort town vibes]
It was like Greece or places like that.
[Full of excitement]
I thought it'd be so nice, so I got very excited.
"Traveling is all about
chilling and resting."
That's what I was thinking.
And the third destination
was exactly that kind of place.
[With instant resort vibes]
Maldives, Bali, Phuket, or Hawaii…
It had those vibes,
[The most anticipated city during the trip]
so I was looking forward to it the most.
My expectations were sky-high.
[A totally different vibe from Cairo and Luxor]
It felt like we came to a different country.
The buildings
looked different too.
[YOHAN looked forward to some rest and relaxation]
A place to rest. A place you go to relax.
That's the vibe
I want to go for.
It was so great.
The reason is,
it was our chance to see the Red Sea.
"I'll get to see the Red Sea!"
[Excited about seeing the Red Sea]
"Oh, I'll get to swim in the ocean!"
I think I was
pretty hyped up about it.
[What DAWN is looking forward to]
Oh, I was really pumped for the resort vibes.
[About the accommodations?]
What kind of things will my accommodation have today?
Since I'll be a prince anyway.
[Even as paupers, a vacation spot sounds great]
I thought a vacation spot would be great for being a total pauper,
[The unique mindset of the Paupert]
since that's a whole different situation.
[Embracing different expectations,]
I was just thinking of fully resting at the resort.
[they head to
their 3rd destination, Hurghada]
[A quick pit stop at a rest area]
[They shop for souvenirs]
[and make local friends]
Thanks, my friend.
It's just really cute.
It's the Alphabet.
[Enjoying their free time
doing what they each like]
- Are you wearing it?
- What?
No.
You're still wearing
that lucky necklace.
[The lucky necklace merchant]
It's nicer than I thought.
[is ice cream shopping]
I'm eating Egyptian ice cream.
[After some time at the rest stop,]
It's my first time using dollars here.
What did you do?
I went to the bathroom.
I went to the bathroom,
but they asked for a dollar.
[they arrive
at the 3rd destination!]
[Hurghada Pier]
Have a seat.
[WANGGEOZ board the boat]
Taking off shoes on the boat is a new experience.
[The reason they boarded the boat]
Wow, the weather is so nice.
I'm hungry.
Let's eat as soon as we get there.
Today, for all of you,
since we've even
rented out the Luxor Temple,
for this shoot,
we also rented
an island in the Red Sea.
Wow! It's really beautiful.
I can give you that.
[Their final destination]
This view is something else.
[Continuing from
the cruise and the temple,]
[a private vacation retreat]
[Let's go to WANGGEOZ's very own island!]
Let's go! Let's finally go!
- We're going!
- Nice!
[Leaving the pier and heading into the Red Sea]
It really feels like we're doing something!
Wow!
It feels really different
now that the boat is moving.
Wow!
This is so great!
Oh, yeah!
This vibe is so nice!
[Can't take their eyes off of the emerald sea]
Oh!
That area over there
is seriously beautiful.
- Wow, this is amazing.
- It's not that deep.
- Oh! You can see that?
- Yeah.
It feels like we're F4 from
"Boys Over Flowers" heading over on this boat.
With the wind and a white sheet,
I can go anywhere.
This is really nice.
But the building colors
are different here.
- Oh!
- Oh, you're right.
[Colorful buildings]
I guess there's no sand here.
- That must be why.
- Because it's near the sea.
[Totally different colors from Cairo]
The colors are definitely different here.
I want to see
the Red in the Red Sea.
[The sunset makes the Red Sea glow red]
I want to see this fiery red sea.
- Later, when the sun sets.
- Yeah.
Wow, this is so nice.
- So nice!
- Wow!
I want to dive right here.
Oh!
- Can you do it from here?
- Yeah.
- It really feels like we're at a resort.
But did ancient Egyptians think
of this place as a vacation spot?
Probably not.
Like, heading out to sea itself...
I doubt they would've
bothered building anything on an island.
I feel like the sea would've been
a completely unknown world to them.
Wow, the color of
the sea is insane.
[Trying to capture
the Red Sea on camera]
- It’s hard to capture it on camera, right?
- Yeah.
It’s nothing like what
we see with our own eyes, right?
Totally different.
[Happy]
There's even a nice breeze! This is so amazing.
Those people don't know
what romance is.
[Relentless speed with zero romance]
This right here is romance.
- They just want to hurry over.
- Yeah.
[Romantic JOHNNY
values vibes over efficiency]
What are you so lost in?
It's just so nice.
The wind is blowing.
The sea looks beautiful.
I feel so happy right now.
We gotta make time
for moments like this.
What do you call this again?
Keeping the romance alive.
It felt like
I stepped into a movie.
There was
this perfect spot on the boat.
I just sat there,
staring out without a single thought.
I also relaxed
while scrolling on my phone.
We also chatted together.
This kind of thing
is what I think is the joy of traveling.
It was such
a precious moment during this trip.
[JISUNG,
another little brother chasing romance]
I definitely will post this.
This is insane, wow.
I think it's my first time
seeing this kind of sea from the top.
It's so beautiful.
Fish!
Jellyfish, jellyfish!
- Jellyfish, jellyfish! Oh, you're right!
- Yeah.
This is amazing.
Dolphins, dolphins!!
Oh?! Dolphins!!!
[Dolphins just
swam right next to us]
[The lucky dolphins
we met here in Egypt]
[※Added stock footage
since we couldn't film a lot※]
(Wow)
It was my first time
seeing wild dolphins.
It was my first time ever
experiencing something like that.
And the view was
just breathtaking.
JISUNG, you like it?
I love it.
The sea is so beautiful.
[By the way]
Is all of this called the Red Sea?
Yes!
How was the Red Sea parted?
Which way did it split?
It split going both ways.
Yeah, so it's both ways.
But like this, or like this?
[Curious which way Moses parted the Red Sea]
One land connected to the other,
so it must have been
from here to there.
- So it split like this?
- Yeah, probably.
But think about it.
It’s from here all the way to there.
Moses parted this, right?
Then, wouldn't it take
days to walk through it?
Probably just a few hours.
Not just a few hours, even more…!
I think it would take a whole day!
I think it's only
a few kilometers long.
It's only a few kilometers long?
[The Red Sea is vast, even at a glance]
But it's super, super far.
It's all the way to there!
(Hmm...)
But now that I'm here looking at it,
I think the story of splitting it
is nonsense.
[Wow, he's denying the Bible]
LEETEUK, you're gonna be in big trouble!
- Oh really?
- LEETEUK, that's…!
[Quick apology]
I'm sorry.
- Hey JISUNG!
- Pretend you didn't hear that.
[LEETEUK / Church oppa]
Everyone, I'm Christian! I mean no disrespect!
[Just so curious because it's so mysterious]
It's more like, how did he part this?
That's why it's Moses' miracle.
That's why
it's Moses' miracle, LEETEUK.
[Church oppa YOHAN
gets caught in LEETEUK’s sight]
Huh?
How do you part the Red Sea?
How am I supposed to know that?
[If you knew the method,
it wouldn't be a miracle]
[Damage control mode]
Now that I look at it again, I think it's possible to part.
[Looks doable]
I think it’s possible.
- Okay, acrostic poem with "Red Sea".
- Yes.
[Acrostic poem with "Red Sea"]
"Red"!
Wait,
why is this so sticky? Hold on.
He's stalling,
he's stalling for time.
"Red"!
"I will part the Red Sea."
[Excited]
Oh!
"Sea"!
"Sea it through!"
- Fail.
SHINDONG!
"Red"!
"Being here at
the Red Sea with all of you,"
"I think 'ALL or NOTHING' will do really well."
"Sea"!
"Sea-hee-hee-hee-hee!"
[Just pushing through with momentum]
You're really good at it, so good.
Wow, I didn't
even think about that!
[15 minutes since departure]
Is that the island
we’re heading to?
Is it that?
That way…Where exactly?
- Where is our island?
- Where's the island we're going to?
[The shape is coming into view]
I think it's that.
- But LEETEUK!
- Yeah?
There’s not a single building.
They said it’s not here,
but over there.
There’s no building there either.
[Staff] Why are you looking at me?
From what I can tell…
That might be the hardest place.
If I had to guess
the production team’s plan,
they seem to think
the start and the end need to be really difficult.
They're even taking us
to an island!
Isn't it supposed to be
"A small beginning, a grand ending"?
It could really
be the most difficult one.
[A mission that allows the princes to leave]
Could it be that the winners
are the only ones
who get to leave by boat?
[Nervous]
It's really far.
We're going a really long way.
(Observing)
There’s a house, there’s a house!
- There is?
- Yeah, there is.
- What's there?
- A house!
- What?
- We’re sleeping there?
[Buildings come into view as they get closer]
It must be that!
- Is that it?
- Wow, that’s really huge!
[Giftun Island, located in the Red Sea
right in front of Hurghada]
[A resort for the princes]
[and a famous spot
with 107 parasols]
[Enjoy the blue Red Sea by day]
[And gaze at
the fiery Red Sea by night]
[The perfect final destination]
Wow, it's seriously
what you see in movies.
[Excited]
Wow, this is insane.
My heart was fluttering.
They said
we rented the whole island.
This is romance.
The entire island is a desert,
[JOHNNY] and it felt like
we used only 1/100 of it.
[SHINDONG] A rocky mountain
shaped by nature.
And a resort built
by humans right next to it.
Hey, I've figured it out.
[LEETEUK] The paupers
will sleep down there.
And the princes
will sleep up there.
Oh, they're sunbeds!
That's a perfect spot
for a solid 6-hour nap.
But it must get
so cold at night.
Yeah, it'll be cold at night.
But how can you sleep
outside today?
[They’re all just worried about becoming paupers]
Everyone's already worried they'll sleep outside.
Everyone's already
thinking about becoming paupers.
But being a pauper
in this setting isn't so bad!
The sand is your bed.
The wind is your blanket.
[Completely forgot his life as a pauper]
LEETEUK, have you forgotten how it was after just two days?
But today,
I really don't need to be a prince.
You don't?
I'm fine today.
- Really?
- Oh, really?
[But if you make me one, I'll be one]
I mean, I wouldn't say no.
I want to be a prince.
Is someone letting you?
Let's go!
[30 minutes after leaving Hurghada]
Let’s go, let’s go!
[Arrived at the island where the last prince will be decided!]
Wow, this is cool.
[DAWN] The big boat couldn't go closer,
so we took a smaller boat
to head to the island's dock,
and it felt like a movie.
Wow, so cool.
This is awesome.
Wow, this is insane.
I feel like we just
stepped onto a movie set.
[WANGGEOZ finally arrives on land]
Wow!
- Wow, this is crazy.
- This place is next level!
This is the place!
- This is the spot!
- The view is crazy!
Seeing that there are
this many sunbeds,
it means that
this many people come here.
[Giftun Island, a tourist hotspot in the Red Sea]
Honestly, I think I could totally sleep here too.
But I feel like
you'd end up eating a ton of sand.
It'd be so cold.
Yes, it'd be so cold.
Wow!
Oh, it’s way bigger!
[Up close, the scale is next level]
Oh, this place is huge!
Look!
There are individual rooms over there.
[When you pass the parasols and head inside,]
Wow, the building is massive!
[you can see the princes' rooms]
I'd be so happy
waking up here in the morning.
This is so nice.
Then, we're the only ones
on this island?
It feels like it's just us.
[The princes’ holiday on a private island]
Wow, that view over there is stunning too.
Wow!
Wow, this place is so beautiful.
This is a view hotspot!
This is insane.
It feels unreal.
- I need to check that area out.
- Wow, this is so cool.
- Wow!
This is amazing!
[Moving on to the princes’ rooms]
Oh, the rooms are here.
Oh, wow!
That’s right.
Oh!
Whoa!
Whoa, there’s a terrace!
[When you enter a prince's room,]
[there's crisp, fresh bedding]
[and an ocean view
you can enjoy lying down]
[A place with a view like this]
I need to be a prince.
(Legendary)
This is one room, like this? Wow, amazing!
Wow!
[LEETEUK] In the morning,
you step out here with a coffee in hand…!
- Wow, this is crazy.
- This place is so beautiful.
[Happy]
Wow!
Is that a pool over there?
- Wow!
- Oh, you're right.
[A pool facing the Red Sea]
They said
there are welcome drinks here.
Oh, please!
- Wow!
Thank you!
Welcome drinks?
[Welcome to Giftun Island]
Pineapple.
Shall we clink glasses?
Sounds good.
- Cheers!
- "ALL or NOTHING"!
- Wow!
- This is so delicious!
Oh, I'm just so happy.
[What kind of fierce battle
will unfold in this calm and relaxed vibe?]
Hey, I have to be a prince today.
[What are you doing...?]
Hey, hurry up!
No, like why…?
[What arrived instead of a fierce battle is]
Why are you so happy? Why so happy?
[Happiness?!]
No, like, why are you so happy?
[All the foods you wanted in one place!]
I can’t resist ramyun! I just can’t!
[This is paradise!]
Wow, this is seriously delicious.
Egypt really knows
how to make a good burger.
[Relaxed laughter
just comes naturally now]
We're reporting live on location!
[When was the last time we were this relaxed…?]
I'm really taking in all of Egypt.
Oh, then…
[A paradise on earth instead of a fierce battle]
This is fun, this is fun.
Wow!
I should’ve come out alone.
[The final hurdle to becoming a prince]
What? How do you play this game?
[A conversation with the ancients]
[Search through the whole island]
Those who find and understand the ancient language
[and find the hidden clues]
will become princes.
I really can’t trust LEETEUK…
[If you want to become a prince,]
Let’s just show one each.
[do whatever it takes]
Want to share? I’ll solve the question for you!
If we keep going like this,
we could both become princes.
[A relentless onslaught]
Please, please!
[of an intense showdown]
JISUNG!
Throw it away.
Seriously, no way!
But…this is really not it.
[Who will be the final prince?]
Wow, then I'm gonna be traumatized for the rest of my life.
I can’t stand stuff like this.